{
    "id": "4876159389af48f5ae50a5b83d77339f",
    "title": "Reported Speech Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I asked him …………………… .. do it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to not",
                "not to",
                "to don't"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The officer asked us …………………… show our proof of identity.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She asked me if I ………………… finished the work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "had",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher advised the boys ……………………… hard.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to work",
                "working",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She inquired if she ………………… leave early.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They asked me …………………… interested in the offer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that I was",
                "if I was",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He said that he ………………… his licence the day before yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "got",
                "get",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He wanted to know when ………………… leaving.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was I",
                "I was",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He suggested ………………… consult a doctor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that I",
                "me to",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He proved that the earth ……………………… round the sun.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "goes",
                "went",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}